Finding Aid for Harlan Henthorne Hatcher Papers
Bentley Historical Library
Harlan Henthorne Hatcher Papers
1837-1998
1891-1986
Bentley Historical Library
Hatcher, Harlan Henthorne, 1898-
851647 Aa 2 Ac
72 linear feet
1 oversize folder
1.1 GB (online)
Harlan Henthorne Hatcher (1898-1998) was president of the University of Michigan from 1951 to 1967. The papers span the years 1837-1998 and document Dr. Hatcher's University of Michigan presidency, Ohio State University career, literary career, organizational involvement, personal life, and family history. Includes correspondence, newspaper clippings, manuscripts, speeches, yearly datebooks, oral history interview transcripts, magnetic audio tape recordings, an audiocassette recording, and photographs.
The papers were transferred from the President's Office (donor no. 343 ) and from Harlan and Anne Hatcher and their family (donor no. 4589 ).
The collection is open for research.
The collection contains audio tapes from which digital copies have been made. Source tapes are for staff use only. Audio files are only available in the Bentley Historical Library reading room on designated Bentley Library computers.
Digitization: The Library has undertaken the digitization of a number of sound recordings within this collection. The resulting audio files are available for playback only in the Bentley Library Reading Room. Links to item images and additional information are available within this finding aid. Original sound recordings are only available for staff use.
Harlan Henthorne Hatcher was best known in his roles as author, educator, and university administrator. He published over seventeen books, numerous short stories, and many essays. At Ohio State University he served as an English Instructor, Assistant Professor of English, Professor of English, Dean of the College of Arts and Sciences, and Vice-President. Hatcher served as President of the University of Michigan from 1951 to 1967.
Dr. Hatcher was born on September 9, 1898 to Robert E. Hatcher and Malinda B. (Leslie) Hatcher of Ironton, Ohio. He attended Ohio State University from 1919-1927, receiving his bachelor's, master's and doctoral degrees in American Literature. In 1925 he completed post-doctoral work at the University of Chicago. Later, Dr. Hatcher spent a year in Italy, France, and England studying the Renaissance.
Harlan Hatcher spent much of his career at Ohio State University. He was an English instructor from 1922-1928, Assistant Professor of English from 1928 to 1932, Professor of English from 1932-1944, Dean of the College of Arts and Sciences from 1944 to 1948, and Vice-President of Ohio State University from 1948 to 1951.
In addition, Dr. Hatcher had an active professional life outside of the university. He wrote over seventeen books about the people, the history, and the geology of Michigan, Ohio, and Kentucky in addition to the subject of English Literature. Several of his short stories and essays were published in journals. In 1937 and 1938 Dr. Hatcher directed the Ohio branch of the Federal Writers Project, and he was the editor of their final product, The Ohio Guide. From 1938 to 1944 he wrote a weekly book critic column in the Columbus Citizen. He was the Editorial Advisor for College English from 1938 to1948, and was guest editor for several other publications. Dr. Hatcher was also involved in the military. He was a U.S. Army Private in 1918 and a Naval Reserve Lieutenant from 1942 to 1944. He served as a V-5 Instructor at the Pre-Flight School in Chapel Hill, North Carolina in 1944.
In 1951 Harlan Hatcher became president of the University of Michigan, a position he held until 1967. Under his leadership, enrollment more than doubled and the budget nearly quadrupled. He oversaw the development of North Campus and the regional campuses in Flint and Dearborn. He revolutionized the university's library system with the establishment of the Undergraduate Library, which was open long hours and had open-shelf access to books.
Dr. Hatcher was an active participator in organizations. His Faculty Personnel Record for the University of Michigan names membership or involvement in over eighty-five organizations through the 1960s. He dedicated his retirement to the problems of pollution and urbanization of the Great Lakes. He was president of the Developing Great Lakes Megalopolis Research Project (DGLMRP), he was on the board of directors for the Center for the Great Lakes (CFGL), and he was a trustee of the Great Lakes Foundation.
Dr. Hatcher's first wife, Frank (Dot) Wilson Colfax, predeceased him. He married Anne Gregory Vance in 1942. They had two children, Robert Leslie and Anne Linda. Harlan Hatcher died in 1998, at the age of ninety-nine.
Summary Contents List
University of Michigan Presidency, 1951-1967 [Boxes 1-59]
Yearly Correspondence File, 1951-1967 (arranged by academic year) [Boxes 1-48]
Organizational Responsibilities/Special Activities as President, 1953-1967 [Boxes 48-54]
Michigan Council of State College Presidents, 1958-1964 [Boxes 48-49]
Midwestern University Research Association, 1954-1962 [Boxes 49-50]
Sesquicentennial Celebration of the University of Michigan [Boxes 50-51]
Commission on the Education of Women (American Council on Education) [Box 51]
Institute for Defense Analyses [Box 52]
Association of American Universities [Box 52]
Citizens Committee on Higher Education [Box 52]
Council for Financial Aid to Education [Box 53]
Joint Office of Institutional Research [Box 53]
Michigan State University (Change of Name) [Box 53]
National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges [Boxes 53-54]
Ceremonial/Public Role as President, 1951-1967 [Boxes 54-58]
Inauguration, November 27, 1951 [Box 54]
Engagements - Invitations - accepted (correspondence) [Box 55]
Speeches [Boxes 56-57]
International Travel [Box 58]
Topical Files, 1951-1967 (arranged alphabetically) [Box 59]
Pre- and Post-Presidential Files [Boxes 60-72]
Personal/Biographical, 1837-1997 [Boxes 60-62]
Miscellaneous [Box 60]
Yearly Datebooks [Box 60]
Interviews [Box 60]
Autobiographical Writings [Box 60]
Family [Boxes 61-62]
Writings, 1918-1991 [Boxes 62-64]
Coursework [Box 62]
Poetry [Box 62]
Books [Boxes 62-63]
Essays and Short Stories [Box 64]
Book Reviews by Harlan Hatcher [Box 64]
Miscellaneous [Box 64]
Ohio State University, 1919-1951 [Boxes 64-69]
Teaching Materials [Box 64]
Clippings [Box 65]
Correspondence [Box 65]
Organizations [Box 65]
Speeches [Box 66]
Dean's Personal and Professional File [Boxes 66-68]
Vice President's Personal and Professional File [Boxes 68-69]
U.S. Military, 1942-1944 [Box 70]
Retirement, 1968-1998 [Boxes 70-72]
Clippings [Box 70]
Correspondence [Box 70]
Organizations [Boxes 70-71]
Speeches [Boxes 71-72]
Travels [Box 72]
Audio and Visual Materials [Box 72]
Photographs [Box 72]
Audio Recordings of Speeches [Box 72]
The Harlan Henthorne Hatcher Papers document his University of Michigan presidency, Ohio State University career, literary career, organizational involvement, personal life, and family history. The collection spans the years 1837-1998, with the bulk of the materials covering 1891-1986. It includes correspondence, newspaper clippings, manuscripts, speeches, yearly datebooks, oral history interview transcripts, magnetic audio tape recordings, an audiocassette recording, and photographs. The collection is strongest in its documentation of Dr. Hatcher's presidency at the University of Michigan, especially in correspondence and speeches. Documentation is weakest on the subjects of his Ohio State University career before 1944 and organizational involvement before 1967. The collection may be useful to researchers interested in the history of the University of Michigan from 1951-1967, the duties of university administrators and their spouses, authors of the 1920's to 1950's, and environmental activism in Michigan in the 1970's and 1980's.
The Harlan Hatcher collection has been divided into two subgroups of files: those which were created or accumulated from his tenure as president of the University of Michigan (1951-1967) and those materials (mainly personal) dated either prior to or subsequent to Hatcher's presidential years.
The library, as archives of the University of Michigan, is the repository for all of the files of its presidents. For historic reasons, all of the papers of presidents up to and including Harlan Hatcher have been treated as personal collections and cataloged under the name of the president. Beginning with Hatcher's successor - Robben Fleming - and continuing to the present, the files of individuals occupying the president's office have been considered both personal and institutional. Records created from an individual's responsibility as president, usually materials from the years when he was president, are treated as office files and have been cataloged as part of the University of Michigan President's Office record group. Materials from either before or after an individual's tenure as president have been treated separately and have been cataloged under that president's name.
Academic freedom.; Authors, American -- Michigan.; Demonstrations -- Michigan -- Ann Arbor.; Disarmament.; Draft.; Education -- Michigan -- Ann Arbor.; Great Lakes Region -- Research.; Greek letter societies -- Michigan -- Ann Arbor.; The Michigan Daily.; Panama Canal (Panama); Poliomyelitis.; Radicalism -- Michigan -- Ann Arbor.; Vietnamese Conflict, 1961-1975.; Photographs.; Center for the Great Lakes (Chicago, Ill.); Cinema Guild (Ann Arbor, Mich.); Developing Great Lakes Megalopolis Research Project.; Hatcher, Harlan, 1898-1998.; Michigan Historical Collections.; Michigan Memorial Phoenix Project.; Michigan Union.; Ohio State University.; Salk, Jonas, 1914-1995.; United States. Army. Reserve Officers' Training Corps.; United States. Congress. House. Committee on Un-American Activities.; University of Michigan -- Administration.; University of Michigan -- Alumni and alumnae.; University of Michigan -- Anniversaries, etc.; University of Michigan. Board in Control of Intercollegiate Athletics.; University of Michigan. Board in Control of Student Publications.; University of Michigan.; University of Michigan. Dept. of Military Science and Tactics.; University of Michigan -- Faculty.; University of Michigan -- Football.; North Campus (University of Michigan); University of Michigan -- Sports.; University of Michigan -- Students -- Societies, etc.; University of Michigan. President.; University of Michigan. Sesquicentennial Office.; University of Michigan -- Students -- Political activity.; University of Michigan -- Students -- Social life and customs -- 1951-1960.; University of Michigan -- Students -- Social life and customs -- 1961-1970.; William L. Clements Library.; Writers' Program (Ohio); Chiang, Kai-Shek, 1887-1975.; Ford, Gerald R., 1913-2006.; Hatcher, Harlan, 1898-1998.; Hatcher family.; Hill Auditorium (University of Michigan); Johnson, Lyndon B. (Lyndon Baines), 1908-1973.; Michigan Union.; Nu, U.; Soekarno, 1901-1970.; University of Michigan. Board of Regents.; University of Michigan -- Buildings.; North Campus (University of Michigan); University of Michigan. President.; American Council on Education.; Baits, Vera Burridge, 1892-1963.; Bentley, Alvin M. (Alvin Morell), 1918-1969.; Bonisteel, Roscoe O. (Roscoe Osmond), 1888-; Bunche, Ralph J. (Ralph Johnson), 1904-1971.; Carnegie Corporation of New York.; Cohen, Wilbur J. (Wilbur Joseph), 1913-1987.; Connable, Alfred B. (Alfred Barnes), 1904-; Council of Ten.; Cutler, Richard Loyd, 1925-; Dewey, Thomas E. (Thomas Edmund), 1902-1971.; Doan, Leland Ira, 1894-1974.; Douglas, William O. (William Orville), 1898-1980.; Economic Club of Detroit.; Edmonson, James Bartlett, 1882-1954.; Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Dwight David), 1890-1969.; Eisenhower, Milton Stover, 1899-1985.; Ford, Henry, 1917-1987.; Ford Foundation.; Hannah, John A., 1902-1991.; Hart, Philip A. (Philip Aloysius), 1912-1976.; Herbert, J. Joseph, 1894-1956.; Hilberry, Clarence Beverly, 1902-; Institute of International Education (New York, N.Y.); Johnson, Lyndon B. (Lyndon Baines), 1908-1973.; Kennedy, Charles Stuart, 1887-1966.; Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald), 1917-1963.; Lawton, James Frederick, 1888-1969.; Matthaei, Frederick C. (Frederick Carl), 1892-1973.; Meader, George, 1907-1994.; Niehuss, Marvin Lemmon, 1903-2003.; North Central Association of Colleges and Schools (U.S.); Nu, U.; Ormandy, Eugene, 1899-1985.; Osborn, Stellanova, 1894-1988.; Oswald, Marina, 1941-; Pierpoint, Wilbur K., 1914-; Power, Eugene B., 1905-; Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1884-1962.; Ruthven, Alexander Grant, 1882-1971.; Salisbury, Harrison E. (Harrison Evans), 1908-1993.; Sawyer, Ralph A. (Ralph Alanson), 1895-1978.; Shriver, Sargent, 1915-2011.; Smith, Allan Frederick, 1911-; Swainson, John B. (John Burley), 1925-1994.; Thant, U, 1909-1974.; Warren, Earl, 1891-1974.; Williams, G. Mennen, 1911-1988.
- University of Michigan Presidency
  Hatcher is the last president whose collection contains a mixture of both personal and office files. The University of Michigan Presidency subgroup is the largest portion of the collection comprising 59 linear feet of correspondence, memoranda, reports, speeches, and other materials on which he acted or which crossed his desk as president. The University of Michigan Presidency subgroup is divided into four series: Yearly Correspondence Files, Organizational Responsibilities/Special Events and Issues as President, Ceremonial/Public Role as President, and Topical Files.
  - Yearly Correspondence File
    The Yearly Correspondence File (47 linear ft.; 1951-1967) series is the largest series in the collection and is further divided into chronological subseries for each academic year. Each year is comprised of a single alphabetical sequence of papers on which Hatcher acted or transferred to another university administrator for action. Included as well are the communications which faculty, departments and other units, alumni, legislators, citizens, and other individuals had with the president.
    - 1951-1952
      - Aa-Az (Box 1)
        (1-1)
      - Acknowledgments (Box 1)
        (1-2)
      - A.F.R.O.T.C. (Box 1)
        (1-3)
      - Alumni Association (Box 1)
        (1-4)
      - American (Box 1)
        (1-5)
      - American Council on Education (Box 1)
        (1-6)
      - Anonymous-Asylum (Box 1)
        (1-7)
      - Applications for positions (Box 1)
        (1-8)
      - Association of American Colleges (Box 1)
        (1-9)
      - Association of American Universities (Box 1)
        (1-10)
      - Association of American Graduate Schools (Box 1)
      - Ba-Bz (Box 1)
        (1-11)
      - Bacon (Deborah) (Box 1)
        (1-12)
      - Baits (Vera) (Box 1)
      - Bennett (Wells) (Box 1)
      - Bonisteel (Roscoe) (Box 1)
        (1-13)
      - Brandon (A.L.) (Box 1)
      - Brown (G.G.) (Box 1)
      - Bureaus (Box 1)
        (1-14)
      - Ca-Cz (Box 1)
        (1-15)
      - Carnegie Corporation of New York (Box 1)
        (1-16)
      - Clements Library (Box 1)
        (1-17)
      - College Presidents Council (Box 1)
        (1-18)
      - Connable (Alfred) (Box 1)
        (1-19)
      - Cooley Memorial Building (Box 1)
        (1-20)
      - Cooley Memorial Building (Box 1)
        (1-21)
      - Council of Ten (Box 1)
        (1-22)
      - Da-Dz (Box 1)
        (1-23)
      - Discriminatory Clause (Box 1)
        (1-24)
      - Doan (Leland) (Box 1)
        (1-25)
      - Ea-Ez (Box 1)
        (1-26)
      - Economic Club of Detroit (Box 1)
        (1-27)
      - Eckert (Otto E.) (Box 1)
        (1-28)
      - Edmonson (James B.) (Box 1)
      - Fa-Fz (Box 1)
        (1-29)
      - Fellowships,Scholarships, Funds,etc. (Box 1)
        (1-30)
      - Fellowships,Scholarships, Funds,etc. (Box 1)
        (1-31)
      - Football (Box 2)
        (2-1)
      - Ford Foundation (Box 2)
        (2-2)
      - Ford, Benson (Box 2)
      - Ford, Henry (Box 2)
      - Foreign Students (Box 2)
        (2-3)
      - Fund for Advancement of Education (Box 2)
        (2-4)
      - Furstenberg (Albert) (Box 2)
        (2-5)
      - Ga-Gz (Box 2)
        (2-6)
      - Gale (Esson) (Box 2)
        (2-7)
      - Governing Boards. Association of Governing Boards (Box 2)
      - Ha-Hz (Box 2)
        (2-8)
      - Hannah (John) (Box 2)
        (2-9)
      - Henderson (Algo) (Box 2)
        (2-10)
      - Herbert (J. Joseph) (Box 2)
      - I (Box 2)
        (2-11)
      - Institute of International Education (Box 2)
        (2-12)
      - Intercollegiate Athletics. Board in Control of Intercollegiate Athletics (Box 2)
        (2-13)
      - J-K (Box 2)
        (2-14)
      - Kennedy (Charles S.) (Box 2)
        (2-15)
      - Kellogg and Kresge Foundations (Box 2)
      - L (Box 2)
        (2-16)
      - Lane Hall (Box 2)
        (2-17)
      - Lecture Committee (Box 2)
      - Lawyers Club (Box 2)
      - Mc-Mac (Box 2)
        (2-18)
      - Ma-Mz (Box 2)
        (2-19)
      - Michigan (Box 2)
        (2-20)
      - Moore (Earl V.) (Box 2)
      - Na-Nz (Box 2)
        (2-21)
      - National (Box 2)
        (2-22)
      - National Defense (Box 2)
        (2-23)
      - Niehuss (Marvin) (Box 2)
        (2-24)
      - North Central Association (Box 2)
      - N.R.O.T.C. (Box 2)
      - Oa-Oz (Box 2)
        (2-25)
      - Pa-Pz (Box 2)
        (2-26)
      - Pierpont (W.K.) (Box 2)
        (2-27)
      - Q (Box 2)
        (2-28)
      - Ra-Rz (Box 2)
        (2-29)
      - Radio (Box 2)
        (2-30)
      - Reddig (Rhoda) (Box 2)
      - Relics (Box 2)
      - R.O.T.C. (Box 2)
      - Residence Halls (Box 2)
        (2-31)
      - Rice (Warner G.) (Box 2)
      - Rowe (Tom D.) (Box 2)
      - Ruthven (Alexander) (Box 2)
      - Sa-Sl (Box 3)
        (3-1)
      - Sm-Sz (Box 3)
        (3-2)
      - Sawyer (Ralph) (Box 3)
        (3-3)
      - Senate Committee on University Affairs (Box 3)
      - Sink (Charles) (Box 3)
        (3-4)
      - Smith (Ira M.) (Box 3)
      - Soule (Malcolm) (Box 3)
      - Stason (E. Blythe) (Box 3)
      - Stevens (Kenneth) (Box 3)
        (3-5)
      - Stevenson (R.A.) (Box 3)
      - Student Legislature (Box 3)
      - Student Publications. Board in Control of Student Publications (Box 3)
        (3-6)
      - Ta-Tz (Box 3)
        (3-7)
      - Thirteen. Committee of Thirteen (Box 3)
        (3-8)
      - Thuma (Burton) (Box 3)
      - Thurston (Lee) (Box 3)
      - U (Box 3)
        (3-9)
      - V (Box 3)
        (3-10)
      - Visitors (Box 3)
      - Vaughan (Henry F.) (Box 3)
      - Wa-Wz (Box 3)
        (3-11)
      - Walter (Erich) (Box 3)
        (3-12)
      - Watkins (Herbert) (Box 3)
      - Williams (R.L.) (Box 3)
      - Williams (G. Mennen) (Box 3)
        (3-13)
      - X-Y-Z (Box 3)
        (3-14)
    - 1952-1953
      - Aa-Az (Box 3)
        (3-15)
      - Acknowledgments (Box 3)
        (3-16)
      - A.F.R.O.T.C. (Box 3)
      - Alumni Association (Box 3)
        (3-17)
      - American (Box 3)
        (3-18)
      - American Council on Education (Box 3)
        (3-19)
      - Annuity Committee (Box 3)
        (3-20)
      - Applications for Positions (Box 3)
      - Anonymous-Asylum (Box 3)
        (3-21)
      - Associations (Box 3)
      - Association of American Colleges (Box 3)
      - Association of American Universities (Box 3)
        (3-22)
      - Association of Graduate Schools (Box 3)
      - Ba-Bz (Box 3)
        (3-23)
      - Baits (Vera) (Box 3)
        (3-24)
      - Bacon (Deborah) (Box 3)
      - Barbour Scholarships (Box 3)
      - Bennett (Wells) (Box 3)
      - Biographical Sketches (Box 3)
        (3-25)
      - Black (Frederick L.) (Box 3)
      - Bonisteel (Roscoe) (Box 3)
      - Brandon (A.L.) (Box 3)
        (3-26)
      - Brown (G.G.) (Box 3)
      - Ca-Ck (Box 4)
        (4-1)
      - Cl-Cz (Box 4)
        (4-2)
      - Clements Library (Box 4)
        (4-3)
      - Carnegie Corporation (Box 4)
      - Commencement, 1953 (Box 4)
        (4-4)
      - Connable, Alfred (Box 4)
      - Council of Ten (Box 4)
      - Da-Dz (Box 4)
        (4-5)
      - Deans (Box 4)
        (4-6)
      - Dedication of Mason-Haven Halls (Box 4)
      - Doan, Ira (Box 4)
      - Ea-Ez (Box 4)
        (4-7)
      - Eckert, Otto (Box 4)
        (4-8)
      - Economic Club of Detroit (Box 4)
      - Extension Service (Box 4)
      - Engineering Research Institute (Box 4)
        (4-9)
      - Pa-Pz (Box 4)
        (4-10)
      - Fellowships, Scholarships, etc. (Box 4)
        (4-11)
      - Fontanna, S.G. (Box 4)
        (4-12)
      - Football (Box 4)
      - The Ford Foundation (Box 4)
        (4-13)
      - Ford, Henry (Box 4)
      - Ford Motor Company Fund (Box 4)
        (4-14)
      - Foreign Language Requirement (Box 4)
        (4-15)
      - Foreign Students (Box 4)
      - Furstenberg, Albert (Box 4)
        (4-16)
      - Ga-Gz (Box 4)
        (4-17)
      - Gale, Esson (Box 4)
        (4-18)
      - Governing Boards. Association of Governing Boards (Box 4)
      - Ha-Hz (Box 4)
        (4-19)
      - Hannah, John) (Box 4)
        (4-20)
      - Henderson, Algo (Box 4)
        (4-21)
      - Herbert, J. Joseph (Box 4)
      - Ia-Iz (Box 4)
        (4-22)
      - Institute for International Health and Education (Box 4)
        (4-23)
      - Intercollegiate Athletics. Board in Control of Intercollegiate Athletics (Box 4)
        (4-24)
      - Intercollegiate Athletics. Board in Control of Intercollegiate Athletics (Box 4)
        (4-25)
      - Ja-Jz (Box 5)
        (5-1)
      - Ka-Kz (Box 5)
        (5-2)
      - Kellogg Foundation (Box 5)
        (5-3)
      - Kennedy, Charles S. (Box 5)
      - La-Lz (Box 5)
        (5-4)
      - Lane Hall (Box 5)
        (5-5)
      - Lawyers Club (Box 5)
      - Luncheons (Box 5)
        (5-6)
      - Mc and Mac (Box 5)
        (5-7)
      - Ma-Mz (Box 5)
        (5-8)
      - Michigan (Box 5)
        (5-9)
      - Michigan Council of College Presidents (Box 5)
        (5-10)
      - Moore, Earl V. (Box 5)
        (5-11)
      - Mott Foundation (Box 5)
      - Na-Nz (Box 5)
        (5-12)
      - National (Box 5)
        (5-13)
      - News Service (Box 5)
      - Niehuss, Marvin (Box 5)
        (5-14)
      - North Central Association (Box 5)
      - N.R.O.T C. (Box 5)
      - Oa-Oz (Box 5)
        (5-15)
      - Odegaard, C.E. (Box 5)
        (5-16)
      - Olson, Willard C. (Box 5)
      - Pa-Pz (Box 5)
        (5-17)
      - Q-R (Box 5)
        (5-18)
      - Questionnaires (Box 5)
        (5-19)
      - Radio (Box 5)
        (5-20)
      - Reddig, Rhoda (Box 5)
      - Regents (Box 5)
      - R.O.T.C. (Box 5)
        (5-21)
      - Revelli, William (Box 5)
      - Rice, Warner (Box 5)
      - Rowe, Tom D (Box 5)
      - Russel Award (Box 5)
        (5-22)
      - Ruthven, Alexander (Box 5)
      - Sa-Sl (Box 5)
        (5-23)
      - Sm-Sz (Box 5)
        (5-24)
      - Senate Advisory Committee (Box 5)
        (5-25)
      - Sink, Charles (Box 5)
      - Smith, Ira M. (Box 6)
        (6-1)
      - Stason, E. Blythe (Box 6)
        (6-2)
      - Stone, Ralph (Box 6)
        (6-3)
      - Student Legislature (Box 6)
        (6-4)
      - Stevens, Kenneth (Box 6)
      - Stevenson, R.A. (Box 6)
      - Student Publications. Board in Control of Student Publications (Box 6)
        (6-5)
      - Ta-Tz (Box 6)
        (6-6)
      - Thurston, Lee (Box 6)
        (6-7)
      - Va-Vz (Box 6)
        (6-8)
      - Va-Vz (Box 6)
        (6-9)
      - Vaughn, Henry F. (Box 6)
      - Visitors (Box 6)
      - Wa-Wz (Box 6)
        (6-10)
      - Walter, Erich (Box 6)
        (6-11)
      - Watkins, Herbert (Box 6)
      - Williams, G. Mennen (Box 6)
        (6-12)
      - Williams, R.W. (Box 6)
      - X, Y, Z (Box 6)
        (6-13)
    - 1953-1954
      - Aa-Az (Box 6)
        (6-14)
      - Acknowledgments (Box 6)
        (6-15)
      - A.F.R.O.T.C. (Box 6)